Guide to the Vehling gastronomy graphics collection.
Vehling gastronomy graphics collection.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Vehling gastronomy graphics collection.
6812
Vehling, Joseph Dommers,
ca. 5.1 cubic feet.
Printed materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Broadsides, wine lists, prints, newspaper and magazine articles, menus, and other graphic materials relating to food and wine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Broadsides, wine lists, prints, newspaper and magazine articles, menus, and other graphic materials relating to food and wine.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Vehling, Joseph Dommers, 1879-1950,
Subjects:
Gastronomy.; Dinners and dining.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Advertising (Box 6)
  6 items
- Art/Artwork (Box 4)
  75 items
- Art/Artwork (Box 9)
  23 items
- Banquets, 1600-1900 (Box 5)
  84 items
- Banquets, 1600-1900 (Box 9)
  5 items
- Banquets, 1600-1900 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  3 items
- Clubs (Box 3)
  20 items
- Clubs (Box 9)
  2 items
- Cookery, 1700s-1800s (Box 3)
  70 items
- Cookery (Box 9)
- Dinners and Dining (Box 7)
  52 items
- Dinners and Dining (Box 9)
- Drinking customs, French (Box 1)
  13 items
- Drinking customs, 1760-1900 (Box 1)
  48 items
- Drinking customs (Box 9)
  1 item
- Festivals, 1800-1922 (Box 3)
  21 items
- Festivals, 1823-1849 (Box 9)
  10 items for Lord Mayor's Day
- Festivals (Box 9)
- Food (Box 7)
  58 items
- Food (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Hotels, 1800s-1900s (Box 7)
  51 items
- Hotel Stationary (Box 7)
- Hotels (Box 9)
- Hotel photographs and posters (Box 8)
- Manners and customs, 1786-1922 (Box 1)
  92 items
- Manuscripts, 1700s (Box 3)
  15 items
- Menus- Europe (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous (Box 9)
- Miscellanea, 1610-1946 (Box 11)
  Binder with items pertaining to food, cookery, drinks, inns, and hotels
- Newspapers, 1700s-1800s (Box 6)
- Newspapers, 1767-1820 (Box 9)
- Personal works, biographical information, artwork (Box 10)
- Portraits, 1800s (Box 6)
  10 items
- Restaurants (Box 6)
- Restaurants (Box 9)
  4 items
- Songs and poetry, 1750-1850 (Box 9)
  22 items
- Tables/table settings (Box 6)
  35 items
- Tables/table settings (Box 9)
- Tables/table settings (Mapcase-folder 1)
- Wines and Beverages, wine lists (Box 2)
  49 items
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Bound publications- cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
Old Inns, etched by Edwin Edwards
Art Treasures from the World's Fair, The Werner Company, 1895.